Contact

anujshrotriya17@gmail.com 8745898503 LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Microsoft Excel · Teamwork ·
Numerical Ability · Microsoft
Office · Microsoft PowerPoint
· Microsoft Word · Customer
Service · Research · PowerPoint

Accomplishments · See all

2 Certifications · 2 Languages

Anuj Kumar

Research Associate at 13D Global Strategy & Research Gautam Buddha Nagar, Uttar Pradesh, India

Summary

Researcher with a demonstrated history of working in the various industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service and Research. Strong research professional with a PGDM focused in Finance and Data Analytics from JRE Group of Institutions.

Experience

Research Associate · 13D Global Strategy & Research September 2018 - Present · Greater Noida

Management Trainee · Wise Finserv March 2018 - August 2018 (6 months) · Noida Area, India

Sales Trainee · Zydus Wellness Ltd.

March 2017 - November 2017 (9 months) · Goa

Intern · Idea Cellular Ltd

May 2016 - June 2016 (2 months) · Lucknow Area, India

Education

JRE Group of Institutions

PGDM, Finance and Data Analytics · (2015 - 2017)